<resources>
    <string name="app_name">acua</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <!-- Sign up -->
    <string name="get_started_button">Get Started</string>
    <string name="get_started_tur1">Get your car washed in the \nconvenience of your own home</string>
    <string name="get_started_tur2">Book an appointment between\n 06:00 and 18:00 7 days a week</string>
    <string name="get_started_tur3">Enjoy convenience</string>
    <string name="terms_title">auca terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_content">Acua Agreements\n\n
You are about to sign up to be an acua end user
By clicking ‘accept’ you confirm that:\n\n
1.	The contract\n
1.1	You have read, understood and agree to the terms of use and the Privacy Policy (the agreements). Any person booking or receiving car wash services provided for by acua agrees to and is bound by these agreements. A summary of the agreements is provided below. This summary is not intended to replace the agreements but is provided for convenience purposed only.\n\n
ACUA TERMS OF USE\n\n
2.	The service\n
2.1	A booking must be made on the app by selecting the wash type on the app, the make of the car to be washed and confirming the availability of the utilities, i.e. water referred to as “tap” and electricity referred to as “power source” in order for the car to be washed. Fill in the desired date, time at location at which the carwash service will be rendered. Select confirm to book the appointment.\n
2.2	We warrant that the services shall\n
	a) Materially comply with the relevant descriptions posted on the app\n
	b) Be carried out with reasonable skill and care and\n
	c) Comply with all applicable statutory and regulatory requirements\n
2.3	We will make every effort to arrive and complete the services on time in each instance, but they may be delays due to circumstances beyond our control in which case we will complete the services as soon as reasonably possible\n
2.4	 We reserve the right to suspend the service if we must deal with technical problems or to make improvements to the service/equipment\n
\n
3.	PRICES/PAYMENTS\n
3.1	Payments should be made via credit or debit card; the payment details must be filled out under the “payments” tab on the acua app. Failure to do so will result in the services not being provided to you\n
3.2	The prices for the carwash services are displayed on the acua app, prices are subject to change and we reserve the right to change such prices at any time by posting new prices on the acua app. All prices are inclusive of VAT unless otherwise stated; we shall determine the size/category of your vehicle in our sole discretion. If the car to be washed does not fit the size/category selected in the acua app, the cost of the wash will be adjusted accordingly\n
\n
4. LIABILITY\n
4.1	You must remove from your vehicle any valuable items which are not connected to your vehicle, we will not be liable/responsible for any loss of or damage to any such items. Please do not ask our operators to remove or store any such items for you as we cannot accept any responsibility or liability.\n
4.2	Child seats must be removed and replaced by you as our operators will not refit in any circumstances\n
4.3	The car must be positioned in the area the user would like for the car to be washed. This area must be near the accessible “tap” and “plug” points. Acua operators will not, under any circumstances, move or drive the car around or to a desired area.\n
4.4	Before allowing us to begin providing the carwash service, you must tell us about any defects, damage or weakness in your vehicle which may affect the services or otherwise relevant\n
4.5	You agree that existing paint chips/scratches on your vehicle may become visible after cleaning and that we will not be held responsible for any lifting and /or flaking to paint work, lacquer, decals and trim (including without limitations wheels) during the valet process where this is a result of an underlying condition which may not be obvious prior to valeting the vehicle. You understand that reasonable care will be taken to your vehicle whilst under our control, but you understand that we will not be held responsible for damage that might occur to your vehicle when we are done with the service\n
4.6	 We shall not accept any responsibility for claims made after the vehicle has been washed and the operator has left\n
4.7	Our total responsibility to you hereunder (including for acts of our employees, agents, consultants and/or subcontractors) shall be limited to the greater of:\n
a) The actual value of any evidenced damage to your vehicle and\n
b) We shall not under any circumstances be liable for any indirect or consequential loss, including without limitation to loss of profits or business or use of vehicle\n
\n
5.	All warranties, conditions and other terms implied by statue or common law are, to the fullest extent permitted by law, excluded from this agreement however nothing herein is intended to limit liability for death, personal injury or fraud.\n

    </string>
    <string name="terms_accept_button">Accept</string>
    <string name="terms_decline_button">Decline</string>

    <!-- Register Phone -->
    <string name="register_verify_phone">Verify your phone number</string>
    <string name="register_verify_content">acua will send SMS message to verify your phone\nnumber.Enter your country code and phone number.</string>
    <string name="register_verify_note">Carrier SMS charges may apply</string>
    <string name="register_verify_sent">Verification code sent</string>
    <string name="register_button_resend">Resend</string>
    <string name="register_button_next">Next</string>
    <string name="register_button_done">Done</string>

    <!-- Register User -->
    <string name="register_user_title">Edit your profile</string>
    <string name="register_user_content">Enter your name and add an optional profile picture.</string>
    <string name="register_user_first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="register_user_last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="register_user_email">Email Address</string>
    <string name="register_user_field_empty">This field should not be empty!</string>
    <string name="register_user_invalid_email">Invalid Email</string>

    <!-- Side Menu -->
    <string name="side_menu_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="side_menu_notification">Notifications</string>
    <string name="side_menu_payment">Payment</string>
    <string name="side_menu_share">Share app with friends</string>
    <string name="side_menu_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="side_menu_terms">Terms &amp; conditions</string>
    <string name="side_menu_copyright">Copyright © 2017 acua Co., Ltd</string>

    <!-- Tab -->
    <string name="tab_title_statistics">DAILY STATISTICS</string>
    <string name="tab_title_booking">BOOKING</string>
    <string name="tab_title_appoint">APPOINTMENT</string>

    <!-- BOOKING -->
    <string name="book_wash_type">Wash Type : </string>
    <string name="book_car_type">Car Type :</string>
    <string name="book_question_tap">Do you have an accessible tap?</string>
    <string name="book_question_plug">Do you have an accessible plug?</string>
    <string name="book_answer_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="book_answer_no">No</string>
    <string name="book_answer_na">N/A</string>
    <string name="book_schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="book_location">Location</string>
    <string name="book_button_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="book_button_update">Update</string>
    <string name="book_update_title">Update Appointment</string>
    <string name="book_error_tap">Due to an inaccessible tap, we can only offer the waterless wash option.</string>
    <string name="book_error_plug">Due to an inaccessible power source, we can only offer the wash and dry option.</string>
    <string name="book_error_both">Due to an inaccessible tap and power source, we can only offer the waterless wash option.</string>

    <!-- APPOINTMENT -->
    <string name="order_list_empty">No Appointments</string>

    <!-- Place Picker -->
    <string name="map_api_key">AIzaSyC6IrVi3PSVo_GzG-0Gx9LvtSvTlQogCGw</string>
    <!-- Country Picker -->
    <string name="country_picker_search">Search</string>

    <!-- Alert View -->
    <string name="alert_title_notice">Notice</string>
    <string name="alert_button_okay">Ok</string>
    <string name="alert_button_cancel">Cancel</string>

</resources>
